[Music]
so
happy sabbath and welcome to the living
manna seven-day adventist church we are
so happy that you are here
with us we are excited about uh the the
topic that we have um for sabbath school
today i know it's going to be a blessing
to many of you
uh just learning about what some
ministries are doing to really reach the
people um those people that are in need
and we and that they are really truly
being the hands and feet of jesus and
not only are we going to learn about
what they're doing but uh by god's grace
it's going to inspire all of us
to
do this work as well because this is
what god has called us to do
so we just want to welcome all of you
again let us know where you're watching
from before we went
live i guess i saw that somebody was
watching from berlin
um in germany and so that was the first
time i've seen not germany but berlin
you know specifically so welcome
um i see toronto canada
yeah please put in the chat where you're
watching from because we are just so
happy that you are that you are here
with us los angeles welcome new jersey
it's another one from uh that's our rick
from canada of course
rick and julie are here uh brother sean
always
wonderful to to see you on here and to
and to hear your voice he's like that
that energy um that like that just that
really live energy of living man in
church we really appreciate it college
dell tennessee not too far from us walla
walla washington
welcome we are so happy to see each and
every one of you
uh we want you to before i forget
because i feel like i forgot last week i
wanna let you guys know that if you have
prayer requests
we want you to put it in the chat
because our prayer team is um they're
they're here
they are
recording your prayer requests brother
terry will be praying over many of them
i'm in the divine hour during our church
service so please put your prayer
request in the chat
also after the sermon today we have
um an afterglow which is an altar live
and i have to tell you this is where we
really connect as the living man at
church this is where we get to know each
other hear each other's voices we can
even see each other's faces you can do
live video
but for those who don't want to
share your voice share your face you
don't have to do that you can just
listen to the prayers to the testimonies
to the prayer requests that are being
shared there that is where you share
like what the service meant to you what
you learned during this sabbath school
time what you learned um in the sermon
or throughout today's worship service
and so
just it is truly a blessing to just be
able to come together and connect there
so if you have not downloaded altar live
you can do that that is in the chat i
saw it earlier but i think we can put it
back in there now so it can be fresh
in the feed and so you can download
altar live and then right after the
sermon you can be a part of that and so
we just really welcome you to
participate in that because it really is
truly where we build community here at
living mana church yeah uh just uh
before we go on i just saw a
prayer request that uh looks urgent and
so i just want to take a moment to just
uh just to stop and pray okay
gregory hall so we put it up on the
screen for those of you that are
watching okay uh please just join us in
prayer i'm not exactly sure what the
issue is okay but let's just pray for a
moment heavenly father i want to lift
gregory hall to you lord uh his fiancee
is apparently having trouble breathing
right at this moment lord i pray we pray
lord as a church we're praying from
around the world right now yeah that um
you would intercede lord and and restore
her breath lord and whatever the
situation is we just ask that you would
intervene in that situation right now
lord and please both give them both
peace and uh and remedy this situation
this is our prayer in jesus name we ask
it amen amen amen
yes let's just keep them in prayer as we
are moving forward um and this is what
we are we are a church family and so
even though we're online and we're not
directly in each other's faces this is
live this is real this is real life um
this is real church um it's just in a
different format and so um we just you
know want you to just know that we are
connected and we care about all your
personal things that you're going
through so just like if you come to a
church and ask for prayer you can just
put in the chat like you know what like
gregory just did we need prayer now so
let's keep um
them in prayer as as we continue to
worship
continue to worship
so yes for those of you who are just
joining us i don't know if we have any
first timers we like to see if there's
any first timers we know we have um
those who worship with us every week and
we're so thankful and appreciative of
everyone who you know comes into this
space to worship with us but if you are
a first time uh visitor with us today
put a one in the chat and while they um
they're doing that for all the everyone
else we would like for you at this time
to share on your social media platform
that you're that you're watching on that
we're live and invite people to
to worship with us at this time and we
also want to invite you to follow us on
our instagram
my living mana that is also the other
way that we are letting people know that
we are here what our programming is all
about on our instagram you will find
little clips of different things we have
done from the sermon the pastor sermons
i should say that pastor myers has
preached also there's uh living mana i'm
sorry not living mana but uh mental
health monday clips of our the topics
that we've covered there uh because
every monday we have we're talking about
mental health and then there's uh clips
from um true health tuesday uh with dr
schweltz and dr reynolds
we also have the um clips from dr pandit
as well and that is on thursday every
thursday evening and so we want you to
follow us there share there because it
is that way where you can just share the
little clips with your friends with your
co-workers with your family members and
say hey this topic might interest you
this is where i go to church this is
where i worship each and every week and
these type of things that they cover
just to give you an idea so definitely
we want you to follow us on instagram
then we want you to share it with others
and share the things that are on there
that you think may be of interest to to
those who
you want to invite to the church and so
we're making it really really easy and
i've said before i don't know how many i
don't know if we can make it any easier
to be able to share and invite people um
to go to church even on sabbath but
really too we really want you to invite
them to the week what our program that's
going on during the week right because
that is like on practical topics that
can be a blessing to so many um we just
finished i mean we did our just finished
our
marriage topics here on sabbath school
but we also just completed that with
relationships on our mental health
mondays as well and i always say that
the doctors are providing
just a wealth of information that i mean
we all can benefit because we all we're
living in these bodies and because of
sin our bodies you know we get sick we
have disease there's just different
things that happen and they are showing
us you know the best way to keep our
bodies healthy um and so you definitely
want to tune into that and share that
with others as well amen amen and uh
we uh have a a special
yes
sabbath school today um and i think it's
a timely one yes i think it's a timely
one
um
okay all right
so yes my mic is
gone to sleep
so what we're gonna do we're going to
have to uh probably switch out
microphones here
okay
all right
so
uh let's go ahead and we're going to
invite
our guests on
so let's bring on luami
and
eric
he just came in and disappeared
all right
uh
eric camarillo right
is your last name cap
you're muted you're muted
so eric calamello cat
camarillo
camarillo yes yes
camarillo all right um well welcome man
luami welcome
you've been here before you've spoken us
first before uh atante is saying welcome
for you um
we're gonna this is what we're gonna do
we're gonna ask both of you to introduce
yourself
we're gonna we're gonna switch out a
microphone real quick
so if you guys would just talk to our
audience and kind of let them know a
little bit about your ministry uh the
ministry you've done uh um
together and just uh we want to talk
about salt that's why you guys are here
and uh just give a uh like i said a
little introduction and then we're gonna
get into some detail of what it means
to do outreach in the community okay
so whichever one you want to go first
um i'll go first um my name is lawamy
richardson i am an associate speaker for
revelation of hope ministries with taj
paklet uh had the awesome privilege of
working with my brother uh eric um for a
few years when i was in orlando um
currently i'm
starting my own nonprofit organization
entitled the i am greater foundation
that focuses on providing scholarships
mentoring and tutoring for kids in the
inner city communities that idea sparked
a little bit right before the pandemic
but it started when we did our
tutoring and mentoring uh uh classes um
in the neighborhood eric when we were uh
down in apopka and the neighboring uh
communities uh offering
uh tutoring services for one of the
neighborhoods that we was working for
and so that passion kind of transitioned
over and so
yeah so that's a little bit about myself
and what i'm doing currently
cool cool uh yeah no it's it's uh
yeah uh lawami and i were actually
roommates for a good a good amount of
time too because we really got to know
each other
um yeah my name is eric camarillo um
president for salt outreach uh
uh you know god inspired the idea back
in 2011 and uh you know it's been about
11 years now we're serving people
experiencing homelessness um
here in downtown orlando
um
and uh yeah no i'm i'm excited to be
here be a part of this so yeah thank you
for
thank you for inviting inviting us
we are so happy to have um both of you
hopefully you can you can hear me if you
guys can hear me put it yeah
yeah yeah okay great great and we were
successful in changing that out
well we are excited to to have you um i
have followed personally i've followed
what
salt has done i think i learned about
salt in 2018 maybe a little bit before
that but i remember we met you at the
asi in orlando
um
and i was impressed from day one
from what the ministry um
is doing so to let tell our audience
what the ministry has done because i
don't want to give it away because i can
because i before we do that let's pray
okay yes and
then
then i want to talk about the name first
okay why that name okay all right so all
right let's pray and then we'll do that
heavenly father we thank you lord for um
giving us this opportunity lord to share
um
um about this ministry today lord and uh
just the timeliness of it lord we just
ask that you would um
uh fill us lord encourage us strengthen
us lord to do what you've called us all
to do and uh bless this this uh sabbath
school this morning is our prayer in
jesus name amen amen amen
so uh
let's talk about the name
yeah so when we
so it was back in 2011 i had just become
an adventist christian it was about a
year year after becoming an adventist
christian and um
you know a series of events happened um
that i believe god was using to really
um solidify my faith and
um you know he inspired the idea for
salt which was really initially to get
young adults together to do practical
and impactful consistent outreach in the
community
and uh so me and three friends we we got
together and we literally
we're in my friend's room and we prayed
all night it was three of us and we're
like god what do you want to call this
thing
and uh and one of the names was was salt
and the acronym was service and love
together
now salt comes from matthew 5 13 you
know that we are the salt of the earth
right
and uh
and you know the acronyms service and
love together i i we felt like at that
time we saw a lot of service
without love
and when i say service without love i
mean going to go and and feed people
experiencing homelessness but hanging
back behind the tables and not actually
engaging with them and loving on them
and interacting with them and and we see
a lot of quote unquote love but without
service right people that say i love
people
but then they don't go and actually act
on that love and
we felt like the combination of the two
really exemplified what jesus defined as
what being the salt of the earth is and
bringing the two together to really um
uh exemplify just who christ is you know
and and what the bible the bible says he
is so
yes all right um
i think that's
i think that's uh
i think that's a powerful
thought it's a powerful approach i think
that like action with no love yeah i
mean
it's easy to say love mm-hmm
without action
right and i think love without action is
not really love right exactly exactly
right
it's not really love so
um
salt
you are the light of the world you are
the salt of the earth
right right um and if the salt loses
its purpose then it's good for nothing
right exactly yeah for and for salt to
really have an effect on anybody
it has to be mingled with that thing
right it has to be intimately mingled
and yeah i think that that's a huge huge
core
uh uh
core of who salt is is that we want to
make sure that we're creating
relationship with people
and you know we we studied some data
recently which is which is crazy and i i
i hope that we can get this data out
more is
we we so from august of 2020 through uh
march of 2022
um salt was involved in helping to end
homelessness for over a thousand people
over 50 percent of those people were
visiting us two or three times a week
and as their frequency of visits went
down so did successful housing outcomes
so so
what that told us was the deeper
relationship we have with someone the
more likely they're going to succeed
right and to move forward um and so that
that was a that was a key finding i
think it you know
kind of uh
really represents a core value of like
who we are
yeah
yeah so you're yeah you're doing you're
doing and not just saying right
yeah amen yeah
tell us and tell our uh viewing audience
a little bit more about the ministry as
far as like i have to say
my
favorite
highest sabbaths that i've ever
experienced have been when i we've just
done outreach i think um goodness that
was the a-man conference i have no idea
what year that was but maybe 2016. and
all week like the entire day from you
know like
i don't know 8 a.m to like 6 p.m we were
just serving people all day and that was
the best
that's just one example one of the best
sabbaths that i've had in doing service
but you your ministry
takes it further first of all you just
don't do it on sabbath number one and
number two because people's needs are
every day but number two you don't just
stop at that initial
service you follow up am i correct with
them yeah yeah so
we operate uh five days a week right now
um we have uh you know
with god's help we have about 35 staff
members at the moment that are serving
over 200 people a day experiencing
homelessness um
and you know we offer 12 different
services so you know behind me here you
can you can see our shower trailer
so we offer showers through a four
bathroom shower trailer to the
unsheltered we also have a laundry
trailer has six washers and six dryers
in it um we do charging stations we do
we're doing mail services for over 600
people right now because they don't have
an address how are they in their
security checks their food stamp cards
you know that kind of thing
um you know we do haircuts
we do case management uh and we do
mental health counseling so there's a
12 total different services we offer
and we also have outreach pastors a part
of the organization so
starting last year in march we hired our
first outreach pastor and we hired and
he graduated from oakwood university we
hired another outreach pastor
this past january because the need was
continuing to grow
shout out to alfredo oh progress
it was our first outreach pastor uh in
march and and joffrey st hilaire was our
second
and uh they do church service on site
because a lot of our friends do not feel
comfortable going into churches right
right you know what they're experiencing
and and also unfortunately
many of the local churches um you know
there are some local churches that that
do not feel comfortable know how to
handle someone experiencing homelessness
in their congregation
don't come here
don't come here we we don't have money
we're not giving you like yeah there are
then there are some locally that that
really know how to really engage with
them and help them and empower them to
take the next step but then there are
others that maybe are not so sure and
how to do that
um you know so they also do group bible
studies four times a week they were
doing it once a week but they begged for
more and more bible study so we we went
ahead and we're doing it four times a
week now
um and then they also do one-on-one like
kind of spiritual counseling kind of
acting as a chaplain for them because
when you're experiencing homelessness
it's hard to process that it's hard to
process like
you know always that question well why
is why did god let this happen to me you
know and and they kind of help them
guide them through that process and once
a year we do calls for baptism as well
um just to give them the opportunity to
be baptized when we first did our
baptisms last year um there were tears
um and they were like you mean you mean
i can get baptized and and our pastor
was like yeah yeah you can be baptized
if you if you really want to and it was
just such an emotional time so
so yeah that's that's another element of
the organization too
so tell me are you so i have so many
questions here but are you
first of all how are you funded and
second are you working like with the
local county like you said case
management so
are you working with the company so we
have we have our own we we are getting
uh some funding from local government um
we all we our case managers are all our
you know they're our staff so
um you know they uh
uh as far as the case management goes
they do a full assessment
they figure out what the needs are
then they refer them out to other
organizations we kind of act with that
front door
refer them out to other organizations
that could help them take the next step
and then they go ahead and uh
if there isn't an organization that
could help them or if there's a long
waiting list
then we'll go ahead and find a creative
way to meet that need ourselves
but we starting in 2020 when covet hit
was when we started to first get some
funding from local government so city of
orlando uh we're here in orlando florida
so city of orlando has given some
funding toward this and orange county
the county we're in has given some
funding toward it and we've even gotten
some funding from dcf
and things like that so so we have about
and you asked about funding so about 50
of our funding is coming from local
government one we're in the process of
of decreasing that over time
um
yeah and the rest of our funding comes
from individuals
um you know like just to give an example
last year we raised about a million 1.4
million
um
about uh 600 000 came from local
government
372 000 came from actually adventists
adventist business owners individuals
or
or foundations and the rest just came
from other sources you know we've had
some sunday churches and some other
groups of people from other
denominations um
and individuals give toward us so
yeah it's been great to see everyone
come together for this kind of work so
yeah i i i have to i have to share this
because it's so i know
yeah
no no listen so so because of the work
that eric and the volunteers and
everybody who's poured into the city of
orlando can you uh tell them eric
the city of orlando acknowledged salt on
what day
oh yeah yeah so so on uh on april uh so
we launched our laundry trailer on april
15th of 2021
and
we invite we did a we want to do a
ribbon cutting so we invited the mayor
the city commissioners came out we had
some other local government leaders um
come out as well some other people
and uh you know we did the ribbon
cutting it was it was cool as a blessing
and at the end of it the mayor surprised
us and he made a proclamation to call
every april 15th salt day in the city of
orlando
amen that's amazing it's my mom's
birthday pam oh wow okay
no that's amazing that's awesome that's
awesome so um because you said 50 of the
funding comes from local government but
are you you're still considered a
non-profit
organization okay so yeah i know this is
we're not at the end but i think we
could mention it now and then again at
the end if people want to
to give and to support uh this ministry
how do they do that
yeah so they can go to uh
saltoutreach.org
um and and uh you know give toward there
um there's also a text number they can
text somersault s-u-m-m-e-r
salt so four four three two one
um we're actually getting a triple
there's a triple match we're happening
right now so every dollar donated is
actually equaling three dollars at the
moment until the end of september
um and uh and yeah and and on the
website there'll be other ways that they
can see how they can give and contribute
and be a part and of course always
looking for volunteers we had 500
volunteers last year give about 5 000
hours so it's a key part of what we do
yeah wow
so lawami what was your involvement in
the ministry and how did you know
how did you all
get together and
yeah so um prior i moved back down to to
orlando and um eric and i met i think we
was no actually was doing an a y at one
of the local churches there
and uh we ate at taco bell that's
originally where we connected
yeah so this you know salt was still
kind of
um
uh still in the process of what what it
is now you know it has been a lot of
work that's gone into it so anyway long
story short i was an outreach
coordinator so
uh part of my responsibilities was so
cold to various churches
share the vision of salt try to work
that church
partnership with salt and try to get
volunteers from the church to you know
to help out and and try to really
implement salt into
every church that we can get into right
and so
how you know a lot of people don't know
how and so
um that was kind of my responsibility
and then i um from there we uh
transitioned
um i'll never forget i was taking a nap
because eric and i was roommates for a
few years and um you're like hey man we
have this great idea you know you work
with with kids and and i know you have a
passion for it why won't you uh
a spare you know head out on and do a um
a tutoring program for one of the
neighborhoods that that we work at and
so that was another responsibility and
it was just so awesome to be able to go
and and visit these kids man and um just
being able to connect and that kind of
planted the seed for me as i you know
transition out of orlando and and and
continue to
um go in the direction that god was
leading me to start my own non-profit to
really help inner city youth and
mentoring and providing scholarships and
and all of those things but it was
started with sultan and seeing the
impact we was making in the city of
orlando and uh really just trying to
share the vision to as many churches we
went to asi when we pulled up and
uh we didn't they just finished the
shower trailer yeah they like a few days
before asi actually pastor pastor myers
we we were doing some interviews that
day i think you recorded a little video
for us
for the shower training yeah so that's
right
so that that's that was my involvement
with salt and so
man just to see where it's at just you
know to where it's at to what it's doing
now it's just been phenomenal to see and
so he's been inspiring a lot of people's
like how can we start a salt in our
community hey can we do assault here and
there so they know i was associated with
them and so i'm always
referring them right back to salt
outreach man you know so what started
off as a need
and eric experiencing he he has a
phenomenal testimony as well of his
experience with hopelessness is what
started
this whole idea and and and to see
what he needed and now providing that
need for others who experience the same
thing it's been awesome to see
really has
well no mommy that's a good segue
because eric tell us about your
experience because i think sharing your
experience will go into my next question
was going to be um helping
other christians who um
want to help and to work with this
community but don't really know how or
what to say or how to interact because
you had mentioned that earlier so tell
us your story and then how you think
um is the best way to encourage other
people and how they can interact and
help
people in the end that are in need yeah
where where did you where did you go to
school to learn how to do this
so i i
i uh i ended up um i studied i studied
social work um
at university of central florida got my
bachelor's there
i got my master's in non-profit
management from that same school um
and then i got some certification so i
got a certification as a as a cmp so
certified non-profit professional and
then a cfre which is certified
fundraising executive
um and so
that all i i was working in hr during
all that time and i was kind of moving
up in the ranks in the hr world and uh
but i i knew and and this i would
encourage anyone if you're going to
school
don't go to school for something that
isn't going to be your calling you know
what i'm saying i think a lot of time
like oh well i'm going to you know i'm
doing this ministry on the side but let
me go to school for what my job is in
and i i don't think that's
i i don't think that's a good use
of our of our education i i would say go
to school for for the ministry that
you're a part of you know that will help
that ministry
um
but to answer your question uh atonte um
i i uh my testimony is long i've gone
through a lot of weird
strange stuff um and one day maybe i'll
get to share it all but i did experience
homelessness um before becoming a
christian
when i was uh 20 years old i was um
had i i was very
i was in a different world back then uh
and i i just all i cared about was was
money and and and success and and that's
kind of what what my god was and uh i
went up there trying to start a business
and it didn't work out
i had money basically for two weeks and
i was i was up there in chicago for six
months
in a car in my car
and uh out to eat to eat meals i would
go to a mexican restaurant you know how
they give the chips and salsa before
your meal i'd go in eat the chips and
salsa and then walk
out wow i would go to 7-eleven bathrooms
and clean up i'll use the bathroom there
um i would uh if i had some money with a
dollar i'd buy a piece of bread from
panera bread rip it in half it's my
breakfast and dinner get a bunch of
butter free butter from them pile it up
and that would be what i would eat for
my my meals
so i know what it's like
to not have access to your basic needs
experiencing homelessness um
and i think that is uh one of the drives
um that has helped to inspire
um this type of work you know um
so yeah that's that's been a blessing
and then you asked about how people can
help someone experiencing homelessness
yeah and how did like i mean just
through your experience right so if
someone was going to
let's just say you did stumble upon
i don't know a church or a group of
christians or whatever how should how
how should they have interacted like
what is the way that you feel is the
most appropriate appropriate way to
interact with those who are in that
space
yeah so um
i get a lot of phone calls from people
um you know people that genuinely want
to help people experiencing homelessness
and we also get a lot of phone calls
from churches too so
when it comes to people um what i would
say is before
you you uh because it's so easy um to be
working with someone experiencing
homelessness and for that to totally
almost make you homeless you know what i
mean because you you just the need is so
great you know and you only have such
limited resources
the first thing i would do is to pray
and ask god god i want to help this
person but what is my limit
so god might tell you my limit's 500
bucks okay so you know once you get to
that 500 range maybe you're buying meals
maybe you helped with the hotel one
night whatever it is once you hit that
500 range and more is being asked of you
you just say hey i i can't i can't do it
you know because you know your limit
that you set with god um and then
obviously
trying to get them linked to an
organization that can help them
um which churches now um we actually
created some programs for churches
where we actually can coach
and empower and equip the church to
duplicate what we're doing in orlando in
their community um
so and then we also have a program we
can provide ongoing kind of consulting
for that church to help them duplicate
this model um we believe this model is
effective um it's proven to be effective
here in orlando and we
our vision is that every metropolitan
area has a drop in center for people
experiencing homelessness even if it's
not
even if it's not us
providing that drop in center service if
it's somebody then that's that's okay
because then everyone experiencing
homelessness in every metropolitan area
will get their basic needs met
which i believe is truly showing
christ's love to these people and
opening that door to
to take things to even you know greater
heights you know what i mean so
yeah let me let me ask you this um and
either one of you can answer this but
so you know
this is an online church
we don't have a church building
but we have members that are
all around the world yes
so
um
this whole
vision eric started with you right one
individual
who said hey let me
let me see what i can do
in helping
you know people that are that are in
need
um if
some of our members some of our people
wanted to start this in their area and
they may not be connected with the
church right right like man i could do i
could spearhead something like this
in my area
do you the salt currently provide
that kind of training where it's more of
more for individuals
versus
a church training uh yeah church
training like yeah
yeah i see what you're saying
we don't have a a model like that right
now and the reason the reason why
is because now i i do think there can be
an individual that says yes i believe
with god's help i can duplicate this in
my city and that's and that's that's
that's the first step right right the
next step would be finding a team
because
you know on their own they won't be
there's only so far you can go so if if
there's a group of people that maybe are
in an area that say we want to duplicate
this
you know then then that will be um that
will be key and then if that's there
then we can go ahead and kind of
mimic what we would do with churches but
for this group if that makes sense yeah
so eric let me let me let me ask both of
you this again
when you started the ministry did you
start it connected to a church
or did you start it
with that small group of people
we did start it uh connected with the
church at first so
now we we i was i was uh i was the
president of the youth or whatever for
one a church a local church and
it was two of my other leaders that we
got together and and had this vision and
and kind of you know started to to do
this
but it was too it a church could not
contain could not properly manage the
ministry
because it's it's too the uh
it's too it's just too big you know i
don't know if that makes sense or not
but it's just yeah yeah it's too much so
so we had to separate from the church
and and create a separate 501c3
nonprofit organization that's a
supporting ministry of the church you
know we're part of asi right right it's
not ministry but but um so yeah i i
don't think it needs to start out of a
church if that makes it it just so
happened that we did but that was
because this it was just the beginnings
you know what i mean yeah
i do i do want to bring up a point
because eric
by the time you got
you didn't just go out there serving
food right randomly there was you did
surveys and things of that nature right
to see what was the greatest need in the
places that you were servicing am i am i
correct in that yeah yeah so so survey
so we we just we started with food with
before the surveys we started with food
but that was just to initially gather
people together because food is is
something that can really bring people
together
then we started to do the surveys yeah
and the surveys is what led
to everything everything that salt is
right now led from us asking the people
that
ourselves what is it that you need
and then we continue to to to oh you
need this okay a year later shower
trailer oh you need this year later you
know two years later a laundry trailer
so so that's kind of what
helped uh to grow the ministry and we we
aren't you know we're not like
you know we what we would encourage
other people to do is we would teach
them from based on our experience
based on what we've gone through just
without all of the
the mistakes that we made you know right
um so we would probably we would
encourage that same yeah we would
encourage that same thing as doing the
surveys to figure out where's the best
place to start yeah
i love that you ask them what they need
because we ought we tend to
automatically go to
um okay let's feed them they need food
which you know many do but
um we actually did uh some ministry um
this was in the bay area and we you know
visited the homeless shelter and they
were saying look what we need um is more
of like
fresh undergarments and things like that
that's what they were saying at that
time um
and and so you know we cut we we made
gift bags that were geared to
what they were saying but i i mean i
like it that you did the surveys um just
to see because there's there's a lot of
re i don't say a lot but there's
resources where they can get
food but they can't get other things
yeah yeah it's it's important even to
interview and tour the local
organizations to see for yourself maybe
you know there was an organization close
to us that was offering showers but they
only had um
four showers
they were they were not well kept so a
lot of people did not like to go and
take showers there and they only were
open four hours a day five days a week
and they were only showering 30 people
we're showering 80 people right now
70 to 80 people a day so they they
didn't even have the capacity to fill
that need
how many trucks how many uh how many
shower
um
[Music]
uh
i don't know are they trucks are the
trailers trailers
their trailers yeah all right how many
of them do you have
so we have one shower trailer right now
we have a clothing trailer and a laundry
trailer uh we have a storage bus
and uh we have we we also have a second
trailer coming that's what should we get
before the end of the year so
okay
do people do people just come like they
just like how does it work how do they
they it's it's mobile so it moves is
that what you do you go to certain areas
and they know do they sign up to say to
say okay i'm gonna be there on this time
this day i don't know how do you do it
yeah we did rotate a lot in the
beginning um
because there's such a great need where
we are right now we've stationed at our
downtown location five days a week
and then we go on our on on another day
we go once a week to another area and
another day we rotate other cities
um and so when they come um we register
them for all the services they need for
that day and we get them in queue for
those services
um and then we call them up to our
check-in window
which will then get them to you know
then send them off to those services
when it's their turn
right
i just absolutely love this yeah i mean
it's a great idea and so exciting yeah
and we don't you know we're
so
we're at a place in
with our church where
we want to encourage people
as i said our church is global so we've
got people in all kinds of different
places
we want to start encouraging our members
and even those that are not our members
our our faith members we call them yeah
they got their local membership where
they are so they're not officially
members of of our church but they still
watch
but we want to encourage people
to
have that
you know
ministerial
entrepreneurial spirit
right where it's like okay what can i do
in my area i got five people in my area
that you know all part of living man or
two people or three people
my my
you know so we want people to start
getting active
and in fact we we're looking at
you know dedicating one week out of the
month and we're working on this talking
about it inspired by
evangelist richardson yeah
he came preach a sermon how long ago uh
probably about a month ago
yeah okay
and your message was about
you know being it you know getting out
of our comfort zone basically and
really as as atante says be the hands
and feet of jesus and and i want to say
and to our and to all of our our viewers
and members
and our guest members and all our lovely
followers you know here at at living
manna we we try to provide so much um
good bible teaching messages practical
learning all throughout the week and i
was telling my husband i was like our
members are quite
full
they are probably have they're very very
full and they need to exercise some of
that you know and it's it's it's time
for
us to to begin to go out there into the
world and be the salt um of the earth as
well
i do want to say one thing because i
know as a as a church as a collective
there's um a lot of young people are
leaving right they they don't really
feel the importance of church and one of
the things that was a huge draw as salt
was a lot of our volunteers were kind of
not engaged in the church and eric and
you can
share more on this but how many of the
volunteers that started off volunteering
ended up being baptized recommitted and
then reconnecting back to the church
because of salt yeah so when we started
um
we we had 40 volunteer leaders i mean
they were we we tried to split up the
work as much as possible because we're
all students and working and doing
other things you know
so um 20 uh half of those volunteer
leaders were all backslid adventists
that came back to the church
um uh through through service through
outreach and through something you know
um
like this something very practical and i
think
i think that's what our our generation
and generations uh you know uh after us
are looking for they're looking for ways
to get involved and and and to see your
church making an impactful
measurable difference in the community
[Music]
yeah i'm about to
see
i i think
one of the reasons why i think a lot of
people
and young people particularly
leave the church not the only reason but
one of the reasons is because
the church talks a lot
and does a lit does little
right so
when when people see that
that
we're not
actually doing what we're what we say
love your neighbor yeah i'm not gonna
love my neighbor i mean i i want to kind
of transition into
uh salt ministry
helping
some um
some immigrants right before i even go
yeah yeah before you go right there i
just want to say
you know i talked about the ministry
that we've done
in service it's been my
by far my most enjoyable sabbath of my
entire life but also for our kids our
teenage kids like they like
they just they love it they love it i
mean their young adults now are you know
in college now but they absolutely like
their their mindset just changes when
we're doing service especially on
sabbath and helping other people like so
i agree that that's what young people
are looking for
and i think when the world sees
see sometimes
the hypocrisy
they're like why would i want
what you have you know why would
when when
you know when christians are
celebrating
the the
ill treatment
of
people trying to find refuge right
how do we look the world in the face and
say yeah
god is love
right
how do how do we do that
um and you know we're getting to the
place now where
and i'm about i'm about to pre i'll let
you know
i'm about to preach about this the
sermon coming up
is about to be
yeah
how can you claim to love god when you
don't love your neighbor god who you
can't see when you don't love your
neighbor who you can't see um
and eric tell us about so that ivor can
like not preach a sermon right yet but
not quite yet but tell us about what
saul is doing with that like with um
immigrants who you find that are in in
need of your services as well
so so
we've seen
different refugees come through um you
know from different countries we have a
syrian family and that and as well and
that kind of thing but we
we have recently been seeing a huge
influx in the past two months of
venezuelan refugees um
and their stories are all all very
similar they walked over 20 2500 miles
from venezuela with their family across
the mexican border
turn themselves over to ice then get
driven to another state just to get
driven to another state and these people
when they finally get to us and and
praise god they find us because i like
there was there was a group of five
that were literally wandering around in
one of the nice neighborhoods here in
orlando and they didn't know what to do
they were just dropped off in a random
place and just they didn't know english
you know they were just trying to figure
out what to do you know and someone had
found them and called us and we went to
go pick them up
but um you know some of them hadn't
showered in over a month because they
don't have access to a shower some of
them barely have eaten they've lost so
much weight and these and their kids
involved too and and that's that's also
very very heartbreaking so they come to
us for services we give them we are able
to provide those basic needs
and unfortunately there isn't a lot of
resources here in in central florida for
these people um seeking asylum um their
asylum dates are not for nine months so
they can't even get uh anything to work
so they literally are forced they can't
make income they're forced to be
homeless and to try and survive until
their asylum day
and you know we by god's grace you know
he's he's helped our team and our team
man they have such big hearts um
we have a great amazing team they um
they were able to house 18 of those 20.
wow and find creative ways to get them
housed and off the street
and you know there's even some shelters
unfortunately they have turned them away
because they don't have ids
you know what i'm saying and it's like
you know we yeah it's it's been
heartbreaking and um
you know it's it's you know but but with
god's help we're we're we're able to you
know we're able to step into the gap a
little bit to help with that so wow
i mean you get to preach your sermon so
i get to just say it right now but i'm
just
you know just listening to this i mean
it is heartbreaking and
for like
as christians like if we think that
god doesn't care about people um outside
of your
border of your country like he does care
about these people he loves he died for
these people just the same as you and i
and if he if you think that he is not
wanting us to help them
just like anybody else that is within
our borders then we're completely we're
wrong we're off on that i mean it's it
this is this is christianity 101.
yeah yeah
yeah i'm i'm excited to hear that
message pastor
uh let me tell you uh
we we
and i believe all of us i mean there's a
gap right now and and and our people the
the people on this call that are looking
for ways to help
these are people experiencing
homelessness potentially close to where
you live maybe in your city all over the
the you know at least here in the us
they're getting bust all over the place
you know
and so um you know maybe together we can
we can have a follow-up meeting to
figure out how we can
you know
figure out how to help these people um
you know uh
as well so yeah we'll see and that's
right that's what i've been thinking
like
for people who
who are saying hey i would like to
lead out like something uh with
something like this in my area right
right maybe we can maybe we can do a
special training for those people so
this wouldn't just hey everybody cuz
it's
we're looking for people who are
seriously like look i want to do
something in my area yeah and i need to
hear
what are some of the ways i can do it
some of the things that i can do yeah
and
we want you know we want
living manna
to not only bless people
through the word
but
we need our people
um
to
be
actively
engaged in hands-on ministry and we need
that to be happening around the globe
yeah
yeah we yeah we do i i believe
i believe that's what god would want you
know he he'd want us to really be
stepping in the gap
for the people suffering in our
communities you know and that's what
he's called us to do and i just want to
say i i there's a ton of comments i'm
seeing come in that are asking questions
i'm yeah i'm actually gonna go through
all of them and i'm gonna answer you
guys so don't don't think i'm you know i
won't answer you because there's a lot
of questions coming in
and i i know we're probably ending here
soon so we just feel free to answer as
they come up feel free to answer oh
really oh okay
all right well i missed a bunch so we
well we'll just admit do as many as you
can or
what you can catch up with um as you're
kind of going through it i'll just say
you know because i'm i'm also seeing
those questions and people are really
engaged which we want them to be they're
like i'm 100 down i want to help i want
to get involved and we want them to get
involved and so this is the reason why
we did this program today to inspire and
just to see the needy you're right this
was so timely like what's going on in
the country right now yeah um
specifically
your ministry can and hopefully the
ministry that we'll all like um
participate in can meet the needs of
people right now
as they are going you know what i did
not hear from eric was what's your
status
he just fulfilled the need of people
that needed help
and and we live in a climate now that
everything has been so politicized
that we forget the humanity of people
like think about how would you feel not
being not being able to shower for a
month how would you feel knowing that
you're going you're you're not stable
you're going from one place to another
and you're not being treated just with
human
dignity you know dignity
you can't feed your children and people
will say well they should have
stayed home well they couldn't feed
their children there either they yeah
it's it's it's so i mean i remember
there was one guy recently um we
we you know he came we met him that day
you know got got him some clothings food
got him a shower
and um we found there's one particular
shelter that we're calling directly
their leader their executive director
and he's making exceptions for these
people to stay temporarily while we try
to get them into housing
and um
and i remember that day we got him into
a shelter at the end of the day
and um
he cried
you know he's like i haven't slept in a
bed in months
no and you know it's just moments like
that that are like man like we need to
we need to do something you know um i i
see a question here no idea how do they
get medical insurance so
assistance medical assistance right so
um
so it so we actually help
we have a partnership with an
organization that gets people ids so
last month they got about 40 people
um ids birth certificates and social
security cards they just use one of our
offices
and uh and so that's how we you know
that's one of the first steps for a lot
of people is getting them the right
identification because their stuff gets
stolen on the street
um you know so
and they lose it and sometimes we even
help store some of that stuff to make
sure that that they don't lose it you
know on the street so
yeah
somebody's saying i want to start
assault in nashville tennessee and i
know you mentioned and we just talked
about
um
you know
trying to plan something where they can
get this information i mean we'd like
for living mana to
to host some online setting where eric
can come back mommy can come back and we
can actually present all that
information so people who want to start
this in their areas can get the
information that they need they may not
be connected to a local church they're
just with us but they have enough people
that they can get a group together that
can do this
so that was candy if candy can message
me um
if she's in the nashville area she can
message me and we can try to oh yeah
you're not you're in nashville
no huntsville ohio
and joined us in the studio actually
today because he's not
he's only about 30 so minutes away but
and that's good i want you to connect
with her lamy i also want us to and
we're just talk this is real time
talking about this but you know host
something
um in the very soon like within the next
couple of weeks and eric and luami we
need you there of course to present um
this information so we'll have some type
of sign up list speaking of that if you
want to get alerts of everything that uh
living mad church is doing um and that
we can send that on the screen or put it
in the chat
um
you text and that should be coming up lm
um lmoc thank you oc
and yeah there it is four five seven six
so if you're not getting alerts please
sign up
send that text right now and then we
will let you know when we're going to do
this um this meeting so if you're
interested in starting uh something like
salt in your city that eric and luami
will even assist at helping to give you
information
about that because i can i can feel the
excitement and the need that people are
feeling and wanting to get involved
the ministry is absolutely amazing
listening to the stories of what people
are are going through
um and what their experiences are like
is heartbreaking but
it's it's heartbreaking to hear those
stories but when you get involved and
help it is
the greatest um that god does allows us
to be able to help for us it helps us it
blesses us it blesses them but it
blesses us as well like you will
it's just an amazing feeling like you
have a great job eric
it was it was always when salt started i
had always dreamed that i would be able
to do this ministry full-time we're
we're an all-volunteer organization for
eight years and uh
i finally was able to quit my job last
year april first and i've been doing it
full time since then
i i can't i can testify that this
brother really believes in what he's
doing
he was finishing his masters he was
working
the job full-time you know you
engage i mean i i never see this brother
sleep and it was because his heart for
people and and i could testify as
somebody who who lived with him and so
this is not just for sure he he really
put his heart blood sweat and tears into
into the people that that he's investing
in and
even finishing his degree he understood
that this degree is connecting to help
people and inspire other people to do
you know fulfill the need in the
community so um he's not someone who
talks a lot but when he does it's it's
very uh
it's very important to hear and and i
appreciate that uh from eric because
he's not someone who talks that he lives
it and he does a lot more
doing than he does talking so i i to say
that was that was before i was married
now my wife make sure i get sleep
you know she when i when i'm about to
comment on posts
nice
that's not a good idea maybe you
shouldn't post that like okay we love
i saw a question about the water tank we
hook up to a we hook our trailer to a
hose
so we make sure that um so the good
thing about that is our water tank can
only hold enough water for maybe 30
showers
with the hose we can do pretty much an
unlimited amount of showers if we have a
dump
connection hooked up um i saw another
comment about you know people
experiencing homelessness don't go to
shelters
sometimes or don't like to go to
shelters um there's there's definitely a
reason for that we surveyed and found
out that a lot of people
got their stuff stolen in shelters
they don't feel safe in shelters um
people would rather sleep in their car
than be in a shelter because of some of
those things
um so that's that's something to
definitely take you know take into
account um
it's not that necessarily that they
don't want to be in a shelter i mean
right now for the past couple months or
four or five months the shelters have
been totally full i mean there's nowhere
for them to go there's there's i mean
the numbers are growing i mean the first
three months of this year
we saw us about 600 new people to to our
services
you know
every month
after that we've seen 200 300 new people
to our services every month it's crazy
it's it's just continuing to grow and
there isn't enough resources out there
you know what i mean so
so yeah
we want
we want people to
uh
understand that
this ministry may not be up their alley
you know what i'm saying like there may
not be a need where they are
right
for this type of ministry but
surveyed maybe not on this scale but
there's a need yeah every community for
yeah but i mean i think survey the need
of your community and ask yourself what
can
what can i do
right how can i get a how can i
uh maybe create a team around me that we
could you know get together and do this
ministry for our community because
that is where
you know you don't keep salt in a jar
right
i mean you keep it in a jar but
the ultimate purpose of it you got to
use it
you got to use it
yeah well and and i do want to i do want
to elaborate on what you just said
because working with eric and working
the homeless you know with the home our
homeless uh friends um
when we started doing that tutoring
thing little did i know that
four years down the road that was going
to be my passion my calling as far as
providing mentors for you know mentoring
for
um inner city youth specifically and and
seeing that there's a need that over 60
46 million
uh young people between the age and
eight eight and eighteen don't even have
a an adult present in their life right
and so
that was my passion but it stemmed from
working with salt seeing the needs
then that that you know
as we uh did the tutoring thing in that
neighborhood eric that seed was planted
little that i know that was going to
blossom so
what started with salt became another
passion for myself and just for
everybody what what whatever need that
you see needs to be fulfilled
do your best to your ability to fulfill
it you know yeah and and i just want to
say um
so we have we when it comes to
presenting salt to other churches and
stuff we definitely have a system in
place that we've
we've used for other churches as well
that have also started we have a branch
in daytona in tampa
a potential branch happening in
tallahassee and we actually have one
near san francisco that's just getting
going
um so
we want you to have a branch in
huntsville alabama yeah huntsville
eventually will be there you know we
have so we have more outreach pastors
wilfredo and joffrey are and myself are
really taking the lead and uh
uh you know we have that system that we
kind of
go and and teach others and and consult
others and that kind of thing so
so yeah it's uh you know um definitely
uh i guess pastor myers um you said you
would like try to maybe coordinate
something
in the future yeah we are definitely we
want to
we want to partner with you guys our
church living mana church wants to
partner with you guys um in
in any way but also to help educate our
members and viewers and how they can do
something like this in their communities
or get
you know just being able to help those
who are in need in their communities and
so we are going to plan and orchestrate
um
a town hall meeting i don't know if
that's
but something where they can ask their
questions you can share they can get the
information and resources and everyone
who's listening to this and you're
wanting to know when that's going to
happen you need to sign up to get our
text alert so you'll know we're gonna
we're gonna
blast it there to so you could know when
we're gonna be doing this in the next
couple weeks i was just
doing some theological thinking
and something just hit me man like
jesus did not just say you are the light
of the world and when you think of the
light of the world right you're thinking
of like
truth
you know what i'm saying you're thinking
of
letting your light shine and people
seeing that and seeing you know
what the truth has done for you
but he couples it with you're the salt
of the earth
so it's almost like on one hand he's
saying
let your light shine you know the truth
your understanding your knowledge that
people should see
what this has done for you
but then salt
is actually
getting out there and mingling and
doing good for the people
you know
we can we can have light but no salt
which is interesting
you know we're going to preach and we're
going to you know this is the truth and
this is the truth and the truth but
if we're not also salt
then we got we're missing half of the
work right
amen
amen yeah pretty much so
i already see a sermon developing i
already see it
i
might be concerned i'm about to preach
right now oh come hold up now he might
find his way in there
i want to thank everyone as i'm as i'm
here i looked at my phone just now and i
see
people are have been donating throughout
this whole thing i mean i think we've
raised almost 1300 bucks um just from
people
watching
so praise god uh thank you guys for
contributing to the work
amen
amen praise god amen yes that warms our
heart yeah
well you're this is not the last time
you're going to see brother eric or
brother luani there was people who
wanted to connect with you lawami about
your youth about i did you see that they
wanted to know how to contact you so
yes i like eric i'll go back to the chat
and comment okay okay okay i saw that
too so um we're definitely this meeting
that we're going to have so we can get
more information on how the rest of us
in our areas can start this type of
ministry doesn't have to be exactly like
it but just you know get something going
that will be happening soon so please
sign up so you can get alerts so you
don't miss it
um but we just want to thank you for you
know just want to thank you for the
ministry like yeah it's such a blessing
those who are being
served by your ministry and for your
volunteers and everybody a part of your
team it truly truly is a blessing it's
inspiring to ever to the rest of us
um and just i just praise god on how
he's using um
your ministry to be able to help other
people it truly is a blessing we just
want to thank both of you for for coming
on and sharing someone who doesn't talk
a lot you did great yeah
eric did you have a video that you
wanted to share
i mean i can i can share a video if
people want to see a visual i don't know
if do people want to see
we want them to see a video yeah
how long is it eric two minutes it's two
minutes oh go share it please okay um
let's see here
yeah i think you just you're gonna share
your screen right yeah yeah
um
let me see here
while he's doing that i just you know
again really encourage everyone to
i mean just
if this didn't inspire you to want to go
out and do something like right now
today even like i i don't know what it i
mean that this ministry and what they're
doing
um
is just impacting people and touching
lives
in areas that
you know
as a church we haven't um
i mean we have adra and we go into
different countries and do great things
in service for and we you know all
support addre and what the church does
there
but in our own local uh metropolitan
cities it doesn't have to be
metropolitan cities just in our own
areas um sometimes the churches are you
know missing uh the boat yeah on that
so
we want to make sure that
this church doesn't miss the boat and
those who are part of this church as
well and hoping that other people will
get involved too but definitely share
your video if can you guys see it right
now can people see it there you go yeah
there it goes all right here he goes
so this is a walkthrough of our services
this is our friend richie he's
experiencing homelessness right now
um but he he uh he agreed to help us
with this video to show what it looks
like so
can you hear it
turn it up a little bit
[Music]
me
bye
[Music]
this do
good
[Music]
amen amen amen that's powerful man yeah
very powerful
very good that's powerful
i'll send the link i'll put the link in
the for people if they want to see it
yes and they can share it as well yeah
they can share it as well
well we just want to uh you know thank
you uh both for
for jumping on um true blessing
yeah
we're
we just looked at the uh
the practical aspect of
of
you know hands-on ministry
and uh
i'm yeah i'm about to talk about the
the spiritual aspect
and how we
how
we approach issues like this
really reflect who we are on the inside
who we really are
on the inside yeah and so um
yeah you know this is uh
one thing that i that can you guys hear
yeah yeah okay um
listen you know
the prophets in the old testament
uh jesus when he came
uh
these people were
sometimes least liked by the people that
professed god
because
the prophets usually weren't they
weren't
condemning
the atheists the non-believer the they
were condemning the very people who
claimed to serve god
and yet were
not showing compassion not showing love
not showing
the attributes of the character of
christ
and um
and that's why they would stone the
prophets
right
um
sometimes we like to hear
how how
how god loves us more than everybody uh
let me stop preaching yeah you're
preaching all right i'm just gonna let
me just say
and the people aren't going anywhere
they're gonna stay tuned yeah stay tuned
because you wanna hear this message and
the
um the link to salt was just put in the
chat you might have to go up just a
little bit and then somebody also asked
if we could re-put the the number that
they can sign up for living mana church
to get notifications because they don't
want to miss that meeting um so if we
can put that as well
um yeah and let me say we what we hope
to do is um
we hope to be able to ultimately
uh
have a dedicated sabbath yes where
we're just you know we're telling our
members and everybody go out into your
community and do your thing right and
we're gonna talk about right so we'll
talk about that you gotta get more
information about that yeah we wanna be
known as a church that is meeting
people's needs i mean we want to we want
them to be fed by the word and their
practical needs but we want to meet
their physical needs as well and so we
want to be known as that and that is our
goal and you guys are a part of that
because you are our church
and you live in all the different
communities around the around the
country around the world so
um we look we look forward to
engaging um with uh this ministry and
these brothers some more and you
participating
so yes this has been an amazing um
sabbath school you know just just to
hear what the ministry is doing
um please continue to worship with us as
we are going to
move into the divine worship service and
you'll you'll hear more about this
sounds like the sermon is going to be
really a blessing
from god
don't forget after the sermon we can all
talk about these things that we're
learning some of the ideas how you've
been inspired uh through altar live
um and so that's right after so make
sure you join that
um but with that we're going to close uh
with prayer but not just close with
prayer if you have prayer requests um
and let's remember to pray for i'm
freaking the uh gregory hall okay yes
and um
in that situation that we prayed for at
the beginning let's keep them in prayer
and if you have any other prayer
requests put it in the chat now because
the prayer team is going to be praying
and brother terry is going to be praying
as well over these prayer requests so
all right let's let's close in prayer
heavenly father thank you lord for
raising this ministry up uh to be
uh the salt of the earth lord i pray
that as we have talked today lord that
um people that are watching from all
around the world uh will be inspired
by this ministry to
to
launch out into their own ministries in
their local areas lord uh please use
them beyond what they what they think is
even capable lord use us beyond what we
think is capable and uh lord we pray
that the members of living manna
will make a difference in this world
um please lord uh you've raised up this
church for such a time as this amen
please help us to fulfill this will as
our prayer in jesus name
amen amen
[Music]
deep down in the south pacific there's
an edenic island paradise that it's hard
to describe with words its beauty is
breathtaking its climate is relaxing its
people are welcoming its culture is
enriching its food is fulfilling and its
water is refreshing
[Music]
perhaps these melanesian islands are
best known in the world by the water
that punches the thirst thousands of
people each day the natural artesian
water of fiji is the number one imported
bottled water in the united states and
is enjoyed in over 60 countries around
the globe
and while most have never seen this
beautiful land
many have been refreshed by its soft and
smooth wall
it is bottled right at the source high
in the unspoiled rainforests of the
largest of the fijian islands
as tropical rain falls upon pristine
rainforest it filters through layers of
volcanic rock
gradually gathering natural minerals and
electrolytes essential for the human
body this life-giving water collects in
a natural artesian aquifer deep below
the surface of the earth protected from
external elements and uncontaminated by
man untouched by humans until you
unscrew its cap and put it to your lips
[Music]
now it's a little pricey in the states
but here in fiji it's very affordable
and we've been blessed by being hydrated
by day after day you see
water is essential to every form of life
every living cell plants and animals and
humans depends on water in fact three of
the five quarts of blood in the blood
vessels of our body is water and of
every ten pounds of our weight seven of
it is water without water to drink life
is just unsustainable
water is also a natural wonder its
chemical formula is h2o
which means for every part of hydrogen
there are two parts of oxygen now oxygen
is flammable and hydrogen readily burned
but when uniting hydrogen and oxygen
into water you have the liquid that has
the power to quench blazing fires and
satisfy burning thirst
water is not only essential for survival
it's also satisfying for life
and in the same way this is exactly what
god is to us
you see just as this fijian water fell
from tropical skies to saturate the soul
of the earth
so too the healing rain jesus christ
descended from heaven to earth to
saturate the soul of our lives and to
revive and refresh our souls
he is the heavenly reign and the living
water
uncontaminated by the pollution of sin
full of the minerals of grace and the
electrolytes of power
ready to fill the empty bottles of our
life
so are you thirsty today
have the longings of your life remain
unfulfilled and empty
have you been drinking from the polluted
springs of sin and selfishness
or maybe you feel yourself dying in a
drought of discouragement and despair
spiritually dehydrated by family issues
health problems
paralyzing addictions
pain for rejection or plaguing
loneliness
will if so hear the words of the living
water to you today
jesus said if any man thirsts let him
come to me and drink he who believes in
me as the scripture says
out of his heart will fall rivers of
living water
as good as it is this fiji water can
only punch me for a little while
for jesus said whoever drinks of the
water from the wells of this world will
thirst again
but whoever drinks of the water that i
shall give
will never thirst but the water that i
shall give him will become in him a
fountain of water springing up into
everlasting life
and so today
let us go to the water source and as we
do christ will not only fill up the
empty bottles of our lives
but he will also export us into the
world as living containers to share the
water of hope in a world that is dying
of spiritual thirst so let us come so
that we can all go
and that the water of life
can freely flow
hey
our bags
and stuff
shaking
driving us thank you for helping us bro
you're welcome you're welcome yesterday
i was praying
thank the lord that he answered the
prayers it was quick
it was fast it was fun yeah so many many
people had
said words of
encouragement prayers it really held me
up for sure yesterday
gave me power last night when we
preached on baptism i preached right
after this
incident took place and
i was weak or like fainting before i got
up to speak but when i was behind that
pope with you it was just your
supernatural power there
all those people came to the front gave
their hearts to christ
and he went eyes last night the spirit
of god moved in a powerful way
the officer just
said that they found our stuff praise
god
special thanks to this guy so the guy we
thought guy who robbed us was actually
the one who's trying to help us
so many people in life they look upon
god as one that's trying to rob our joy
a god that just wants to make our life
miserable with a whole bunch of
restrictive burdens but we don't realize
that the very one that we think is
trying to rob us is the one that's
trying to save us
mercy upon us
so we're in the police station now we
can't really
film here inside we're gonna continue
this story later on
[Music]
i was uh
14 years old i stole a whole bunch of
things and i got caught and i got
arrested
just like you know handcuffed had to sit
in
jail and i felt so bad
so i know how you feel man today i get
to travel all over the world and help
people share hope to others even though
i made mistakes in the past god still
has a plan and a purpose for us same
thing he did for me he can do for you
too man
do you know jesus
you've heard about it before
god on the cross man to forgive us of
our sins
god has a prayer for you he loves you
he wants to use you to do great things
let him change your life you're 17 years
old you can be anyone you can do
anything with your life you probably
felt like you had to
steal so you can get money to take care
of your family or whatnot but when you
serve god he's going to take care of me
so i want you to know that we love you
brother god loves you man
all right
can i pray with you
father in heaven lord i want to pray for
my brother here lord this is your son
and you love
you die for him
and you have a great plan and purpose
for his life
and i pray lord that he would turn his
life over to you
you would help him to
use his energy his time and his his
talents and his influences
to do good in the world pray that you're
helping to feel
your love and to feel your forgiveness
and i pray lord that
he and his family will be in your
eternal kingdom but we never have to
steal and never have to grow hungry
and thank you lord for hearing this
prayer
in christ's name amen
i'll be praying for you man i'm not
gonna forget you
i hope that you won't forget me too
and uh god loves you man
before we leave just wanted to thank
thank you and
and your wonderful team
uh overnight we were able to find all
our all our possessions most of it at
least and
that was very quick thank you guys so
much for taking the time going
door-to-door and just helping us it was
a very devastating experience yesterday
keep you focused in prayer as you
continue to keep this community safe
that the angels will protect you as you
seek to protect others i'm wondering if
i can just have a prayer
for you father in heaven lord i want to
thank you so much for your great love
and your mercy towards us lord i want to
thank you so much for the officers and
the law enforcement the team here suva
and how they quickly responded and they
did their jobs well
but we pray lord that you'd send angels
to protect each one of them i asked lord
in jesus name that you'd bless each one
of them from the crown of their head to
the soul of their feet bless this police
station and everyone that works here we
pray that angels would be always in this
place
we thank you for hearing and answering
this prayer in jesus name we pray amen
god bless amen yeah thank you brother
thank you great job thank you
thank you this is the man who helped us
so last night when we preached at our
seminar we told the experience of what
happened
and so happens the deputy police
commissioner of fiji was watching our
program and he responded and he called
all his his workers
and uh told them that we needed that
they needed to solve the case
and so praise the lord and the lord used
him to answer the prayers of his people
and so we just want to praise god for
that
okay so we just got a text on my phone
dear pastor bula vinaka i spoke with you
a while ago i hope you are satisfied
with the work of my officers
i was unhappy when i watched your
grievance last night during the seminar
there is a cell in my house attended by
the community members i immediately
contacted my officers
to immediately follow up and i am
thankful that you have experienced the
service we provide
deputy commissioner of police we're very
satisfied
we're gonna go back to the
river to the waterfall the devil stopped
us
yesterday but
not for long
nothing can stop god's work so we're
going to go back we're not going to let
the devil win let's go
told me sorry you know when i was about
his age i was arrested before
so just about 24 hours ago right here at
this exact spot the devil stole my
camera equipment he didn't steal my joy
he didn't steal my peace tried to stop
god's work but god's work can't be
stopped so we're here again
by god's grace even though yesterday he
stole my camera equipment
we were able to steal some souls from
his kingdom
as last night over 50 people here in
suva responded to the baptismal peel and
gave their hearts to jesus so the lord
has already won the victory
the devil's a heated defeated enemy
all he can do is all he can do is
distract us
god has won the victory wow what an
amazing day we had today
from the tragedy of yesterday
we experienced triumph today
yesterday was a mess today is the
message
yesterday was the test today is the
testimony
yesterday we were victims
but by god's grace today we remain
victorious in christ
with all this happening we just want to
thank god and
even though we had a difficult time
yesterday we still love fiji
fiji time
[Music]
for
let's go
[Music]
so
all right if you can hear me put a one
in the chat
um i was just saying welcome welcome
living mana church family we are so
happy that you are here with us today
okay
all right there's a one so you can hear
me continue to put a one i see one one
all right all right
welcome welcome welcome
and we are just so happy that you're
here uh let us know where you're
watching from put in the chat
we love to see it if you just if you
were already
with us during sabbath school time you
don't have to re-put it but if you are
new to our church service um please let
us know where you're watching from so we
can do a special welcome to you if this
is your very first time
uh
watching uh living mana church online
with us put a two because there's a lot
of ones going up right now but put it
too if this is your very first time
worshiping with us we want to say a
special uh welcome to you i see we have
bakersfield california
we have uh maryland san diego
it's like we have all right um so
welcome
from the carolinas colorado
denver colorado
special welcome to all of you we are so
happy got a lot of californians today
amen amen my home state
um pennsylvania maine
i heard it's beautiful in maine haven't
been there want to get there montana
haven't been there but i heard that's
beautiful as well welcome
florida welcome
um texas
all right tahiti i want to go there i've
been wanting to go there so
welcome
um welcome um the
um kevin from tahiti thank you for
worshiping with us today new jersey
oregon antioch california special
welcome to all of you we're very happy
that you were here with us if you missed
sabbath school today man did you miss a
treat but it's okay you can go back and
watch the replay um it was truly an
inspirational testimony of what um the
ministry salt is doing um in the in that
community in florida and orlando and
actually different areas um of florida
as well and so
we've been inspired here at living mana
church and so we are going to
definitely be connecting with salt they
are going to do a presentation for our
church and for our members and for our
guest members um so you can get involved
in learning how you might be able to do
a ministry like that in your community
so if you have not already signed up for
our alerts that you can get from our
church whenever we're doing something
i want you to do that now that's going
to be on the screen
how you can do that you can text
i don't want to mess it up so i'm going
to let it come on the screen it's about
to come on the screen now about how you
can sign up for
the alerts there it is text lmoc
four five seven six and then you will
get these alerts about when we're i'm
gonna have that meeting with salt also
when we're going live with our weekly
programming our mental health mondays
true health tuesdays our prayer meeting
um our service with a doctor our meeting
with dr pandit as well as you know
people are really growing and learning
as they are just learning how to prove
the existence of god without uh i always
say without even using the bible but
just using other things dr pandit is
really educating us on that and so we
just praise god but we don't want you to
miss any of those things that we are
doing we want you to be reminded so if
you sign up you will get alerts about
when all of our meetings are happening
and also you don't want to miss that
very special meeting that we're going to
be doing with salt ministry so we can
learn how we can um start ministries
like that in our own local communities
because that's really what this is all
about i mean we get so fed here um on
living uh in this church uh for living
manna we have we have pastor myers my
husband who who feeds us every sabbath
we have great guest speakers we have
during the week we are fed through those
who lead out in that and so we get a
wealth of just spiritual food and it is
a blessing to our lives practically but
we want to go out and do service for
others that god has called us to be the
salt of the earth and so we want to meet
people's needs their physical needs
whatever it is that we can do for other
people to to be the the hands and the
feet of jesus we want to do that and we
want to equip you
our members our viewers we want to help
you to be able to do that in your
community so
definitely sign up to get the alert so
you can know when uh the meeting is
we are just and we have just been so
blessed you know i was just thinking
like our very first sabbath was april
9th and god has really been blessing um
this this church this ministry and it's
because of you it's because if you're
faithful you guys show up every sabbath
you show up during the week you've been
financially giving and truly god is just
showing us like yes this is what i've
called you to do at this time and
because it is touching people's lives in
such a way he is really really blessing
and so we just praise god because it was
a leap of faith it was us you know we
stepped out into the unknown not knowing
exactly how would this work what will
this look like well people really uh
come back week after week and we see
that it's happening and so we just
praise god uh we praise god for each and
every one of you i want you to know um
this you know our church is a church we
believe in prayer our prayer team is an
amazing prayer team and they lead out
every wednesday for power wednesdays um
and it is such a blessing but they are
right now live
waiting and looking for your prayer
requests they want to pray pray over
your needs
and so please put in the chat uh what
your prayer needs are brother terry is
going to get to many of them in a few
moments here when he leads us in prayer
but i also want to see if we can put in
the chat the email for the prayer team
and so you can email them your prayer
request and they will pray over your
prayer requests you'll get an email
letting you you know that they've been
praying
over your request um and so please put
that in the chat your prayer request
it's there now prayer at living manna
dot live that is the email that you can
use to email your prayer request and
trust me this prayer team they don't
just say we're gonna pray for you they
pray for you so please put that um in
the chat
um we want to let you know how you can
can can continue to support the church
uh we say thank you because so many of
you have been financially supporting the
church and we just want to say thank you
but we just want to let you know how you
can continue to do that there's various
ways that you can do that one of the
ways is that you can give your offering
through cash app and that is as you see
on the screen it's dollar sign living
mana church and you can give your
offering that way you can also go to our
website
which is
livingmana.church and you can click on
the offering tithe
button there and you will be directed to
adventist giving adventist giving has a
virtual tithe envelope you can give your
tithe there the tithe that you give
supports the northeastern conference
which is the conference that this church
living mana church is in and that
supports the worldwide church you can
also give your offering there which
supports living mana church and um the
things that living matter church is
doing so that helps us to be able to get
all the equipment we need to be online
to be able to continue to do ministries
that we offer during the week and to
begin to launch new ministries and so
you can adventist giving and you put
living mana church in there
and you can be able to give that way you
can also mail in
your tithe and offering and the address
is there on the screen the po box 428
owens crossroads alabama 35763
and just just note on a piece on the
check or envelope how much is for tithe
how much is for offering so we can make
sure that it goes to the right place and
we are just very thankful for your
faithfulness it is truly uh blessing uh
the church so that the church
can can do the things that god is
calling us to do we have a very faithful
team that we are working with and our
board members and we are trying to do
exactly what god is calling us to do for
this time so we can get the gospel out
to the world and we know that you know
all of you know so many people are
online right they're online they're on
their smartphones and so that's where we
want to show up we want living mana to
show up right there where they're at so
we can introduce to them uh the things
that god has led us to share you know we
know so many we know so many people are
dealing with mental health issues or
health issues
they need prayer some people just don't
even believe in the existence of god
there's other ministries that we want to
begin to share as well as as part of
living manna's programming and so
with all of that
people are are on on their phones online
and we want to have our advertising
right there so they can see it all they
have to do is click on it and they will
they will be blessed and god the holy
spirit will do the rest and so we just
that is that is our goal and when you
give you are supporting uh the ministry
for us to be able to continue uh to be
able to reach people the advertising
that it takes to be able uh to do that
online and so we thank you for your
faithfulness we thank you for your
prayers we really know that you are
praying and that you support uh this
church and this ministry that god has
called us to do at this time
and at this time i'd like to just pray
and thank all of you for uh your prayers
and for your giving and just ask god to
continue to bless this ministry so that
we can go into all the world uh with the
gospel if you please just bow your heads
with me as we pray
dear heavenly father lord we thank you
um just so much um just
lord the way you're leading
um and in people's hearts for brother
eric the the testimony and the ministry
that he started um with salt lord
we all need to be inspired to do
something like that in our communities
so we just thank you for how you lead in
our lives to want to help and to connect
with people and so lord we just praying
that you would use this church that you
would use our members our our faith
members those who who watch um every
week but maybe a member of another
church we just pray that you would use
all of us to to do exactly um and to do
ministry in a practical way like salt is
doing and just reach the people in our
own communities and lord we we know that
you have called us all to do this in a
specific way and so just show us
reveal that to each individual on how
you want them to do it lord i thank you
for those who have been giving
financially to the church to support
what we are doing here we they are so
faithful and we just praise you uh for
putting that upon their heart as well
lord we ask that the holy spirit we
continue to be with the rest of our
service that it will be a blessing to
those who are live viewing live right
now and for those who will watch later
we just pray that the holy spirit would
penetrate their hearts you know the holy
spirit and you know their individual
situations so let the message and the
music and the prayers speak to them in a
very special way we ask all these things
in jesus name amen
[Music]
don't you be
afraid
joy comes in the morning
[Music]
troubles they don't last always
for
there's a friend in jesus
who will wipe your tears away
and if your heart is broken
[Music]
just lift your hands and say
oh
i know that i can make it
i know that i
can stand
no
matter what
may come way
[Music]
my life is in
your head
praise the lord saints
although
that amazing worship song was
interrupted i want to say
we know that our life
is in his hand
and if you can say that with me today
you know that your life is in the
master's hand why don't you just put a
hallelujah right there in the chat this
morning saints
i know my life is in your hands
i want to give you god praise today and
we want to thank him for allowing us
to serve in this living man of ministry
thank god for
drawing us and for blessing us and
keeping us through our storms and
through our trials yeah i see you in the
chat they're saying hallelujah
everywhere you're watching from and
listening from
praise god we see all the beautiful
saints of god
and as we prepare to go to the throne of
grace we just want to start off today we
want to enter into the courts god's
courts with thanksgiving in our hearts
want to enter his courts with praise i
want to just lift him up and magnify him
it can look crazy sometimes it can look
impossible sometimes it can look like
you ain't gonna come out it's gonna look
like you about to lose your mind gonna
look like you at the end of your wit
hold on saints
don't give up
don't give in don't let go of your faith
like brother todd said this morning
thank god for turning our tests
into a testimony i want to thank god for
taking our messes what's a mess today
and making it a message tomorrow
somebody watching right now you a
message and thank god for your being
here and leave here today and go out and
be a message to somebody tomorrow
and so precious father as we come before
the throne of grace
god we give you praise we ain't here
trying to put on no show we mean it
because we've been through it and we
don't seen it we thank you o father for
being so good and so gracious so loving
and so kind thank you for everyone
listening
in and around the globe thank you for
the trials you brought us through that
taught us how to trust in you more thank
you that when we were without you are
our provider thank you lord god that
when uh we were in trouble you are our
refuge and strength and a very present
help thank you oh god that you never
gave up on us thank you to a patient
loving and kind and we just give you
glory lord we thank you that you are
greater
than our lack of knowing greater than
our distortions greater than the
mountains that stand before us greater
than the obstacles in our way god
greater than the weakness that we are
aware of in our own bodies greater than
our tendencies to stray oh god your
grace is greater than our sins
hallelujah and we just give you praise
we magnify you we choose today to lift
you up god because you are worthy you
are worthy we thank you that you are
alive and on the throne we thank you
that you are listening today and that
you hear the prayers of the righteous
who come before you lord god trusting in
you and leaning upon you in jesus name
and so lord today we just want to thank
you especially lord first we just want
to give you praise for this ministry
salt
salt's out there doing it god they're
doing it and we pray that we'll be
inspired today that the church listening
would be inspired heavenly father to uh
you know as we're out there you said go
feed my sheep and we're trying to do
that lord god in your in your strength
and power but may we mingle some salt in
that food we're laying before these
people in the world that are hurting
that are dying that are lost give us uh
love and compassion lord in our service
that we take time to because some people
lord what they need more than anything
else they don't really care what we know
until they know and can look us in the
eyes and know that we truly care that
we're truly sincere that we're serving
them in the name of one who is touched
with the feelings of their infirmities
father god when some people just need
their decency their dignity back some
people just need that contact back with
humanity again with somebody just need
to know that somebody cares and that
their life is worth something thank you
jesus for filling our hearts with that
love and father we thank you for living
around the church i thank you for pastor
amaya and sister atonte who are family
who are friends who are pastors to us
and counselors to us lord and lights and
examples thank you for this amazing
ministry and this amazing vision and
what you are doing even before today's
discussion thank you for the living
manna church board who have been already
discussing ways to get mobilized and to
get out there and do things lord god
you've been showing us some incredible
stuff thank you for beautiful gifts like
sister janet abby and
some of the awesome amazing ministries
that she's doing it was i was just so
amazed to sit with her in her home and
listen to some of the things that she's
doing lord and some of the amazing
miracles and some of the changes in the
way you're impacting people's lives out
there lord who need it the most lord i
thank you for these 12 practical areas
of ministry that brother eric camarillo
is talking about with salt lord god lord
help just give us the wisdom to know how
we can get out and meet those needs we
may be in our immediate environment
right here in our own little sphere of
influence we may not do all that salts
do but there's something we can do and
so open our eyes lord that we might see
what it is you would have us to do that
has been the prayer request
of many of our beloved saints today they
put it in the chat
and we'll go through that lord thank you
for that but many are asking that you
would speak to their hearts and show
them what you would have them to do
thank you for those prayer requests we
know you will answer lord help our eyes
to be open lord help us not to be so
busy arguing with folk who somebody
didn't look at us the right way didn't
speak to us didn't like our post or
didn't answer the right way we argue
about some crazy little stuff when
there's really some big needs out there
that need to be met and we need to be
getting out there and doing those things
and so jesus we thank you
that you understand and you know even us
lord what we're in our blindness and our
ignorance and our southerners and our
sometimes uh so caught up in ourselves
and what's going on in our lives you get
it and lord i thank you that you're
patient with us and bringing us out of
that thank you that you put some sauce
hallelujah in our water today lord to
get us inspired and up and moving and so
lord i thank you for bringing it right
into my home thank you for my lovely
wife amra and some of the things that
she's getting us involved in right here
in our own community do thank you for
that lord in jesus name lord and i thank
you for brother lawamy richardson lord
in revelation of hope and brother taj
and the wonderful things that they are
doing thank you for the mentorship it is
so important that uh young
men and and women in the inner city need
to have a strong godly mentorship lord
god and godly examples and we just pray
that you continue to blow the wind of
your spirit into their cells as they are
opening wide see how you would lead them
and how you would direct them god i also
want to pray lord god for what does
jesus look like ministries up there in
spokane washington uh brother sean and
crystal cox lord god i know that they
are doing all they can do right there in
their little spirits experi of influence
thank you for their hearts lord having
hearts to help those who are out there
brother sean's getting out there in
those streets and lord god he's got a
he's a ball of fire we pray you protect
him and camp your angels about him give
them to give him the wisdom to know how
to connect with these folk and what to
say and what to do lord supply for his
resources in jesus name because i know
he needs help dear lord and we thank you
that you are the great provider
lord i want to pray for sister janice
morrison's mother uh uh
her who's roof collapsed and and and
homes become inhabitable and so lord she
doesn't
have she's got to have a place to stay
we pray you take care of her and comfort
her it can be quite a shock and lord in
any of the emotional and psychological
uh uh things that are going on with her
lord god but until she can get this her
home repaired and restored take care of
him and watch over lord sister carolina
collado's father has been struggling for
several weeks with getting his cancer
treatment lord jesus just step right on
in and heal touch save and deliver do
something awesome and amazing for you
are the great provider lord god it is
really you we're waiting on and so we
pray for gwendolyn vines also father uh
uh uh she's praying that she would be
able to launch out
and and i know that's the voice of many
today they want to we want to launch out
father i want to spread our wings and
open our borders and and just move out
there and to do the things that you
would do many are a timid and many are
afraid you told timothy that you've not
given us a spirit of fear but a power
and of love and a sound mind and some
people just don't know yet lord but let
them dip their toe in the water and
experience jesus working in and through
them and become addicted to the ministry
hallelujah to seeing jesus do uh both
will to will and to do in and through
their lives and i just pray that that
will be uh the testimony of many today
god and god we're praying for
a jane smith lord she wants a fresh
baptism of the holy ghost god i need
that myself and i know many listening
today need it lord uh we have a sister
who's been saying that she feels cold
and feel that you're distant from sister
natalie kelly is praying lord that you
will speak to her show her in this
drought season of her life lord you're
actually letting her to get her roots
down deep lord god so when the winds and
the rains and the storms come she won't
be blown away and she'll know her god be
strong and do exploits lord we're
praying for nessa b he's asking for a
change heart she's at the labor lord she
wants to be able to show love and
forgiveness to others you already
promised to do it god in jesus name and
i just pray that over these coming days
and weeks you'll be able to lie get in
alignment with you through your word and
through prayer we thank you for brother
gregory hall lord we're continuing to
pray for his fiancee that it will be
totally recovery and we're praying for
downsview uh church that they would
review his transfer and he would get
transferred over to living manna
ministry he has an awesome health
message and some awesome insights he's
been a blessing to the men and we thank
you so much for his presence and our
character building class and some of the
amazing contributions you've used him to
bring to us and we just pray
strengthening build him up be a wall
about him oh lord a flaming wall of fire
around this beautiful brother in jesus
name god and um lord we're continuing to
play for sda uh rail24 uh her kids are
in an sda school and she wants to be
able to keep them there needs financial
assistance watch over her and provide
for her jehovah jairo we thank you in
jesus name and alicia she's praying for
uh
alice and uh
germany lord god that they would uh uh
come back to you lord god and marcellus
bishop who is experiencing some mental
health lord that he would be able to get
the treatment and the health that he
needs uh brother vance's is is is
praying lord god that
that uh uh his friend's heart would come
back to you lord god so we're just
praying you uh reach out and call them
today in jesus name and couture fleming
she's praying for malik lord god that he
would also admire that their hearts
would also be drawn back to you in jesus
name and lord our young brother enoch
who's in nursing school now who is a
such a blessing to us and we're watching
you mold and shape and change this young
man so so precious lord god to see such
a young soul and a young heart with zeal
for you and hunger for you and thirst
for you and he's so thoughtful and
reflective god we just pray that you
bless bring him up out of his comfort
zone he he sensed that you're giving him
that little nudge and so let him stir up
the gift that is in him lord god as so
many other young men of our young men
need lord god don't let them be caught
up into these trends and these fads and
these movements that are going on in
society today that the god of this world
are using to lure our young men away
thank you for young men like enoch lord
uh we're also praying with our sister
michelle watson grant who's praying for
our special couple and a family lord god
that they would be able to overcome they
would be able to come closer to you that
their marriage would be blessed lord god
and we know you're hearing these prayers
many of our marriages sister gigi really
emphasized to us that many of our
marriages are under attack right now
lord and so we are praying oh god that
you will help us here at living manna
ministries our prayer team lord god our
women's and men's um who are doing the
character training under the pastor
seven week program that we would be able
to come alongside and support them and
serve them lord put words in our mouth
give us uh words from the testimonies
and and give us words from scripture
lord and give us light and ways to be
able to open up the sanctuary message
and show them that the answer is in the
everlasting gospel there's never been a
problem that hell has ever came up with
that heaven hasn't already cooked up an
answer to and so we thank you god that
their solution your way oh god is indeed
in the sanctuary and so as we're going
through this program help us oh lord god
to speak words of comfort and words of
wisdom and guidance and support may they
hear your voice and not even ours lord
to help these uh beautiful people come
through these marriages and experience
the power of the god of reconciliation
and lord we're also praying for honey's
mother's health she needs deliverance
from um and and and from anger and lord
i just pray that you watch over her
touch your body and this in anger can
sometimes be uh directly connected to
the health issue lord i know that
personally you delivered me from
debilitating anger and rage and hatred
and i saw you just take the stony heart
out and put in a heart of flesh and give
me a heart of love and found myself uh
back in the days lord god when when my
heart became callous and cold i found
myself
crying over the smallest uh a diaper
commercial so i know you can tenderize
the heart you can make the heart soft
and tender and sensitive you can do it
god and so we just pray set her free
father from these chains
and lord god again we want to pray with
brother ian nichols who who's dealing
with uh liver cancer lord god we pray be
a healer step in lord god and be a
physician to this lovely one lord we
want to also remember to thank you for
sister patty she's always in the chat
and always being encouraging always
laboring always doing the work of the
lord always coming alongside and so we
do thank you for that and brother
lawrence nagy is asking for prayer for
evelyn nicole and salome who have health
issues lord god and gwendolyn who's out
of touch with her family we pray god
that you would um just step into these
situations as we lift these beautiful
ones up before you sister tina wright
and her family are going through stress
and change right now and need your
presence in a special way lord jk petit
has a friend kp who is resisting jesus
lord your word says this is the goodness
of god that leads us to repentance and
so as we begin to close this time of
intercessory prayer father we lift you
up knowing
that you are the good god no matter how
dark it is your word says the light
shineth in darkness and the darkness
overcometh it not those who have prayer
requests that we may have overlooked
today or didn't miss and maybe thinking
well nobody's thinking about me and i
got missed today and maybe my problem's
too big for god lord there's nothing too
hard for you and we just pray for your
revelatory power to just burst upon
their hearts and their minds god you who
commanded the light to shine out of
darkness shine now in the heart of your
people to give the light of the
knowledge of the glory of god in the
face of jesus christ and we o lord will
give you all of the glory all of the
honor and all of the praise all god
saints declared
amen amen
um just wanted to um
give another um thank you brother terry
for that prayer and the prayers um as we
continue to to lift up all those
requests the prayer team will be praying
over your prayer request and i want you
to also pray about something else to put
it put a one in the chat if you have
been blessed by the reflections of hope
that um evangelist taj paclip
shares with us each and every week i
know that i'm personally blessed by them
i know many of you are as well
but you can put a one in the chat uh so
this request is for that ministry um he
i just spoke with him just saw him and
spoke with him this past weekend you
know and he had shared that um he has 15
uh maybe 20 of these um reflections of
hope you know this um just sitting on a
shelf that they need to be the the
footage has been filmed but he is in
need of an editor uh an editor that can
can put these as you guys see it's very
well done he is a perfectionist and so
he makes sure that uh his his
presentation that he presents to us and
to the world is very well done and so he
is in need of an editor uh to be able to
uh finish these 15 that he has 15 to 20
that he has right now um and he will be
producing more and so if
uh you um if god puts it on your heart
uh that you would like to
be able to assist uh
evangelist taj um in this ministry by
editing the footage that he already has
i mean
you can reach out to him and his email
is is on the screen it's taj
pacleb gmail.com
and you can send him a message and say
hey i'm interested in helping you edit
these projects um and you guys can can
work everything else out uh together so
if if you are talented in that area if
god has given you a gift in that area
and you have a heart for ministry and
want to see
those reflections of hope
messages go out into the world then
definitely contact
brother taj and again his his contact
information is on the screen
and so with that we're going to continue
to worship uh god today together
just god bless you and happy sabbath